<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LOTR Scenario Generator</string>

    <string name="generate">Generate</string>
    <string name="second_activity">Second activity</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="tot_the_river_title">To the River</string>
    <string name="to_the_river_a">  Emerging from the forest you must now make your way to the river. As you leave the forest behind, you notice that you are being pursued and thus quicken your pace.\n\tSetup: Each player reveals 1 card from the top of the encounter deck, and adds it to the staging area.</string>
    <string name="to_the_river_b">  As you approach the riverbank, a fearsome Hill Troll emerges from behind a grouping of rocks, and attacks!\n\tWhen Revealed: Search the encounter deck for 1 Hill Troll (if one is not already in play), and place it in the staging area. Shuffle the encounter deck.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while any Hill Troll cards are in play.</string>
    <string name="to_the_river_points">8</string>

    <string name="anduin_passage_title">River Passage</string>
    <string name="anduin_passage_a">  You are able to board a raft and embark upon a river voyage. As you depart, your enemies pursue, harassing the small vessel as you attempt to navigate the river.</string>
    <string name="anduin_passage_b">  As your enemies harass the raft, it is difficult to maintain balance and effectively fight them off.\n\tReveal 1 additional card from the encounter deck each quest phase. Do not make engagement checks during the encounter phase. (Each player may still optionally engage 1 enemy each encounter phase.)</string>
    <string name="anduin_passage_points">16</string>

    <string name="ambush_on_the_shore_title">Ambush!</string>
    <string name="ambush_on_the_shore_a">  Your enemies have forced you into an ambush! If you survive this, the path to safety should be open.</string>
    <string name="ambush_on_the_shore_b">  When Revealed: Reveal 2 encounter cards per player, and add them to the staging area.\n\tSkip the staging step of the quest for the remainder of the game.\n\tOnce there are no enemies in play, the players have won the game.</string>
    <string name="ambush_on_the_shore_points">0</string>

    <string name="the_necromancers_tower_title">Captured!</string>
    <string name="the_necromancers_tower_a">  While scouting near the enemies former lair, one of your allies was ambushed by orcs, captured and is now held in a dungeon cell.\n\tSetup: Search the encounter deck for the first 3 objective cards, reveal and place them in the staging area. Then, shuffle the encounter deck, and attach 1 encounter to each objective card.</string>
    <string name="the_necromancers_tower_b">  When Revealed: Randomly select 1 hero card (among all the heroes controlled by the players) and turn it facedown. That hero is now considered a prisoner and cannot be used, damaged or collect resources until it is rescued.\n The players, as a group, cannot play more than 1 ally card each round.\n\tPlayers cannot advance to the next stage of this quest unless they have at least 1 objective card.\n\tAfter the requirements are met to advance to the next stage, flip the prisoner card face-up and place 1 damage token on it. This hero has been rescued and may now be used by its controller.</string>
    <string name="the_necromancers_tower_points">9</string>

    <string name="through_the_caverns_title">Through the Caverns</string>
    <string name="through_the_caverns_a">  Finding a hidden entrance into the dungeons, you attempt to make your way through the caverns. You need all the resources you can get to find your way.\n\tIf Nazgul of Dol Guldur is not in play, search the encounter deck or discard pile for Nazgul of Dol Guldur and put it in play.</string>
    <string name="through_the_caverns_b">  The players, as a group, cannot play more than 1 ally card each round.\n\tIf there are less than 3 objective cards in play, search the encounter deck for the first objective cards, reveal and add them to play until there are 3 objective cards in play. Shuffle the encounter deck and attach 1 encounter card to each newly revealed objective card.\n\tPlayers cannot advance to the next stage of this quest unless they have claimed 3 objective cards.</string>
    <string name="through_the_caverns_points">15</string>

    <string name="out_of_the_dungeons_title">Out Into the Open</string>
    <string name="out_of_the_dungeons_a">  Following the sunlight, you discover an opening leading out to the side of a hill. Stationed in the open, however, is a large group of Orcs.</string>
    <string name="out_of_the_dungeons_b">  If Nazgul of Dol Guldur has not yet been in play, search the encounter deck and put him into the staging area. Shuffle the encounter deck afterwards.\n\tForced: At the beginning of each quest phase, each player places the top card of his deck face down in front of him as if it just engaged him from the staging area. These cards are called orc guard and act as enemy with: 1 hit point 1 attack and 1 defense.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while Nazgul of Dol Guldur is in play.</string>
    <string name="out_of_the_dungeons_points">7</string>

    <string name="orc_war_party_title">Orc War Party</string>
    <string name="orc_war_party_a">  Your Party journeys through the land while suddenly they stumble upon a group of orcs!</string>
    <string name="orc_war_party_b">  Each player searches the encounter deck for the first Orc card and places it into the staging area. Shuffle the encounter deck.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while there are Orc cards in play.</string>
    <string name="orc_war_party_points">8</string>

    <string name="dark_woods_title">Dark Woods</string>
    <string name="dark_woods_a">  Your party hears rumors about an orc warleader in the woods nearby.</string>
    <string name="dark_woods_b">  If chieftain Ufthak is not yet in play, search the encounter deck for Chieftain Ufthak, put him in the staging area and shuffle the encounter deck.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while Chieftain Ufthak is in play.</string>
    <string name="dark_woods_points">8</string>

    <string name="daring_rescue_title">Daring Rescue</string>
    <string name="daring_rescue_a">  You discover the lair of the evil brood of Orcs and their Hill Troll Leader. You must destroy their hideout and any captives they have taken.</string>
    <string name="daring_rescue_b">  Search the encounter deck for a Hill Troll card and put it into play.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while there are Hill Troll cards in play.</string>
    <string name="daring_rescue_points">8</string>

    <string name="ancient_path_title">Ancient Path</string>
    <string name="ancient_path_a">Long has an ancient enemy hidden in the dark wilderness of Mirkwood. The evil within has plagued the land for years. The time has come to put an end to this darkness.\n\tSearch the encounter deck for Ungoliant\'s Spawn and put it out of play.</string>
    <string name="ancient_path_b">When all progress tokens have been placed on this quest, put Ungoliant\'s Spawn into the staging area.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while Ungoliant\'s Spawn is in play.</string>
    <string name="ancient_path_points">9</string>

    <string name="deep_catacombs_title">Ancient Crypt</string>
    <string name="deep_catacombs_a">Before long the twisted trees before you give way to a large, shadowy clearing adorned with the ruins of an old keep. In the centre, a slippery stairwell descends into the gloomy depths of the catacombs. There you find a huge ornate set of double doors leading to an ancient crypt. There is only one way to find out what evil stirs within.</string>
    <string name="deep_catacombs_b">If the Shadow Key is not yet in play, search the encounter deck for the Shadow Key, place it in the staging area and shuffle the encounter deck. Place one encounter card on the Shadow Key for each player.\n\tPlayers cannot put progress tokens on this stage unless a hero controls the Shadow Key</string>
    <string name="deep_catacombs_points">8</string>

    <string name="risen_nightmare_title">Risen Nightmare</string>
    <string name="risen_nightmare_a">  Gingerly you open the door and step through. You wind your way to a labyrinthine maze of tunnels, half buried forests, underground rivers and dark caves. From deeper caverns you can hear unearthly shrieking.</string>
    <string name="risen_nightmare_b">  If Nazgul of Dol Guldur is not in play, search the encounter deck and put him next to the staging area. Shuffle the encounter deck afterwards.\n\tWhen all progress tokens have been placed on this quest, put Nazgul of Dol Guldur into the staging area.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while Nazgul of Dol Guldur is in play. </string>
    <string name="risen_nightmare_points">6</string>

    <string name="goblin_gate_title">Goblin Gate</string>
    <string name="goblin_gate_a">  From here you must break through the orc phalanx at the dreaded Goblin Gate to get through Mirkwood. An alarm cry goes up and from the gate emerges a swathe of shrieking orcish troops. They have been waiting for you.\n\tEach player searches the encounter deck and places the first orc they find in the staging area. Shuffle the encounter deck afterwards.</string>
    <string name="goblin_gate_b">  The swarm of evil orcs seems unending. You quickly realise you must escape through the gate with post haste. Working your way slowly towards the entrance, you see with a sinking heart that a small army stands fast in your way.\n\tEach player immediately chooses and engages 1 Orc.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while there are Orc cards in play.</string>
    <string name="goblin_gate_points">12</string>

    <string name="elf_path_title">Elf Path</string>
    <string name="elf_path_a">  You march into the darkness of the woods. From the boughs above you a voice calls out. A nimble Elven figure drops to the leafy ground before you. "Hurry - follow me." Your guide darts down a hidden path through the trees and you struggle to keep up.</string>
    <string name="elf_path_b">  You decide to follow the elf through the woods. Behind you evil creatures gather in number and regroup, following hot on your heels. Time is of the essence!\n\tDo not make engagement whilst on this stage. Enemies already engaged with you remain engaged.\n\tYou are neither allowed to engage nor to be engaged by enemies unless you are already engaged with them.</string>
    <string name="elf_path_points">5</string>

    <string name="the_veil_of_the_lonely_mountain_title">The Veil of the Mountain</string>
    <string name="the_veil_of_the_lonely_mountain_a">  In the distance you can see a mountain. Your pursuers emerge around you as you hasten your way to the mountain.\n\tEach player searches the encounter deck and places the first Orc they find into the staging area. Shuffle the encounter deck.</string>
    <string name="the_veil_of_the_lonely_mountain_b">  The Elves have sent help to you. Upon arriving they immediately join you into battle.\n\tEach player may immediately place 1 Elf from their hand into play for free and any Elf character may heal 1 wound. Each player immediately chooses and engages 1 Orc.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while any Orc cards are in play.</string>
    <string name="the_veil_of_the_lonely_mountain_points">10</string>

    <string name="foul_tower_title">Foul Tower</string>
    <string name="foul_tower_a">Your party stumbles upon a dark tower hidden in the thickest undergrowth. With great care you approach the entrance.\n\tSetup: Take out Ungoliant\'s Spawn from the encounter deck and set it to the side out of play.</string>
    <string name="foul_tower_b">As you work your way through the bushes towards the entrance, Spiders hiss and spit at you from all sides. The thunder of their giant leader coming closer can be heard as you quicken your pace.\n\tWhen 5 progress tokens have been placed on this card, put Ungoliant\'s Spawn into play.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while Ungoliant\'s Spawn is in play.</string>
    <string name="foul_tower_points">10</string>

    <string name="twisted_caverns_title">Twisted Caverns</string>
    <string name="twisted_caverns_a">  You rush into the darkened caverns. Moving carefully through the webbed tunnels. Your route to the surface is cut off.\n\tIf Ungoliant\'s Spawn is not in play, search the encounter deck or discard pile for Ungoliant\'s Spawn and place it to one side out of play.\n\tAllies may no longer enter play or be put into play for the remainder of the game.</string>
    <string name="twisted_caverns_b">  From the darkness of the twisting passageways ahead, an enormous shape scuttles to and fro.\n\tWhen 5 progress tokens have been placed on this card, put Ungoliant\'s Spawn into play.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while Ungoliant\'s Spawn is in play.</string>
    <string name="twisted_caverns_points">10</string>

    <string name="final_stand_title">Final Stand</string>
    <string name="final_stand_a">  The caverns open up into a giant underground spider lair.\n\tIf Ungoliant\'s Spawn is not in play, search the encounter deck or discard pile for Ungoliant\'s Spawn and place it to one side out of play.\n\tAllies and Attachment may no longer enter play or be put into play for the remainder of the game.</string>
    <string name="final_stand_b">  A massive silver thread descends from the ceiling and the spiders around you begin to frenzy as a huge dark shadows fall over you.\n\tWhen 5 progress tokens have been placed on this card, put Ungoliant\'s Spawn into play.\n Players cannot defeat this stage while Ungoliant\'s Spawn is in play.</string>
    <string name="final_stand_points">10</string>

    <string name="general_quest_title">Monsters!</string>
    <string name="general_quest_a">The presence of the enemy is getting stronger. You press on but you can feel dark powers nearby.</string>
    <string name="general_quest_b">Each player draw a card from the encounter deck and adds it to the staging area.</string>
    <string name="general_quest_points">8</string>

    <string name="spider_image">spider</string>
    <string name="tree_image">tree</string>
    <string name="orc_image">orc</string>
    <string name="footprint_image">footprint</string>
    <string name="river_image">river</string>
    <string name="eye_image">eye</string>
    <string name="raven_image">raven</string>
    <string name="tower_image">tower</string>
    <string name="progress_1a">1a</string>
    <string name="progress_1b">1b</string>
    <string name="progress_2a">2a</string>
    <string name="progress_2b">2b</string>
    <string name="progress_3a">3a</string>
    <string name="progress_3b">3b</string>
    <string name="information">i</string>
    <string name="information_scenario">Welcome</string>
    <string name="progress_image">image</string>
</resources>
