<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LOTR Scenario Generator</string>

    <string name="generate">Generate</string>
    <string name="second_activity">Second activity</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="tot_the_river_title">To the River</string>
    <string name="to_the_river_a">  Emerging from the forest you must now make your way to the river. As you leave the forest behind, you notice that you are being pursued and thus quicken your pace.\n\tSetup: Each player reveals 1 card from the top of the encounter deck, and adds it to the staging area.</string>
    <string name="to_the_river_b">  As you approach the riverbank, a fearsome Hill Troll emerges from behind a grouping of rocks, and attacks!\n\tWhen Revealed: Search the encounter deck for 1 Hill Troll (if one is not already in play), and place it in the staging area. Shuffle the encounter deck.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while any Hill Troll cards are in play.</string>
    <string name="to_the_river_points">8</string>

    <string name="anduin_passage_title">River Passage</string>
    <string name="anduin_passage_a">  You are able to board a raft and embark upon a river voyage. As you depart, your enemies pursue, harassing the small vessel as you attempt to navigate the river.</string>
    <string name="anduin_passage_b">  As your enemies harass the raft, it is difficult to maintain balance and effectively fight them off.\n\tReveal 1 additional card from the encounter deck each quest phase. Do not make engagement checks during the encounter phase. (Each player may still optionally engage 1 enemy each encounter phase.)</string>
    <string name="anduin_passage_points">16</string>

    <string name="the_necromancers_tower_title">Captured!</string>
    <string name="the_necromancers_tower_a">  While scouting near the enemies former lair, one of your allies was ambushed by orcs, captured and is now held in a dungeon cell.\n\tSetup: Search the encounter deck for the first 3 objective cards, reveal and place them in the staging area. Then, shuffle the encounter deck, and attach 1 encounter to each objective card.</string>
    <string name="the_necromancers_tower_b">  When Revealed: Randomly select 1 hero card (among all the heroes controlled by the players) and turn it facedown. That hero is now considered a prisoner and cannot be used, damaged or collect resources until it is rescued.\n The players, as a group, cannot play more than 1 ally card each round.\n\tPlayers cannot advance to the next stage of this quest unless they have at least 1 objective card.\n\tAfter the requirements are met to advance to the next stage, flip the prisoner card face-up and place 1 damage token on it. This hero has been rescued and may now be used by its controller.</string>
    <string name="the_necromancers_tower_points">9</string>

    <string name="through_the_caverns_title">Through the Caverns</string>
    <string name="through_the_caverns_a">  Finding a hidden entrance into the dungeons, you attempt to make your way through the caverns. You need all the resources you can get to find your way.\n\tIf Nazgul of Dol Guldur is not in play, search the encounter deck or discard pile for Nazgul of Dol Guldur and put it in play.</string>
    <string name="through_the_caverns_b">  The players, as a group, cannot play more than 1 ally card each round.\n\tIf there are less than 3 objective cards in play, search the encounter deck for the first objective cards, reveal and add them to play until there are 3 objective cards in play. Shuffle the encounter deck and attach 1 encounter card to each newly revealed objective card.\n\tPlayers cannot advance to the next stage of this quest unless they have claimed 3 objective cards.</string>
    <string name="through_the_caverns_points">15</string>

    <string name="out_of_the_dungeons_title">Out Into the Open</string>
    <string name="out_of_the_dungeons_a">  Following the sunlight, you discover an opening leading out to the side of a hill. Stationed in the open, however, is a large group of Orcs.</string>
    <string name="out_of_the_dungeons_b">  If Nazgul of Dol Guldur has not yet been in play, search the encounter deck and put it into the staging area. Shuffle the encounter deck afterwards.\n\tForced: At the beginning of each quest phase, each player places the top card of his deck face down in front of him as if it just engaged him from the staging area. These cards are called orc guard and act as enemy with: 1 hit point 1 attack and 1 defense.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while Nazgul of Dol Guldur is in play.</string>
    <string name="out_of_the_dungeons_points">7</string>

    <string name="orc_war_party_title">Orc War Party</string>
    <string name="orc_war_party_a">  Your Party journeys through the land while suddenly they stumble upon a group of orcs!</string>
    <string name="orc_war_party_b">  Each player searches the encounter deck for the first Orc card and places it into the staging area. Shuffle the encounter deck.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while there are Orc cards in play.</string>
    <string name="orc_war_party_points">8</string>

    <string name="dark_woods_title">Dark Woods</string>
    <string name="dark_woods_a">  Your party hears rumors about an orc warleader in the woods nearby.</string>
    <string name="dark_woods_b">  If chieftain Ufthak is not yet in play, search the encounter deck for Chieftain Ufthak, put him in the staging area and shuffle the encounter deck.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while Chieftain Ufthak is in play.</string>
    <string name="dark_woods_points">8</string>

    <string name="daring_rescue_title">Daring Rescue</string>
    <string name="daring_rescue_a">  You discover the lair of the evil brood of Orcs and their Hill Troll Leader. You must destroy their hideout and rescue any captives they have taken.</string>
    <string name="daring_rescue_b">  Search the encounter deck for a Hill Troll card and put it into play.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while there are Hill Troll cards in play.</string>
    <string name="daring_rescue_points">8</string>

    <string name="ancient_path_title">Ancient Path</string>
    <string name="ancient_path_a">Long has an ancient enemy hidden in the dark wilderness of Mirkwood. The evil within has plagued the land for years. The time has come to put an end to this darkness.\n\tSearch the encounter deck for Ungoliant\'s Spawn and put it out of play.</string>
    <string name="ancient_path_b">When all progress tokens have been placed on this quest, put Ungoliant\'s Spawn into the staging area.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while Ungoliant\'s Spawn is in play.</string>
    <string name="ancient_path_points">9</string>

    <string name="deep_catacombs_title">Ancient Crypt</string>
    <string name="deep_catacombs_a">Before long the twisted trees before you give way to a large, shadowy clearing adorned with the ruins of an old keep. In the centre, a slippery stairwell descends into the gloomy depths of the catacombs. There you find a huge ornate set of double doors leading to an ancient crypt. There is only one way to find out what evil stirs within.</string>
    <string name="deep_catacombs_b">If the Shadow Key is not yet in play, search the encounter deck for the Shadow Key, place it in the staging area and shuffle the encounter deck. Place one encounter card on the Shadow Key for each player.\n\tPlayers cannot put progress tokens on this stage unless a hero controls the Shadow Key</string>
    <string name="deep_catacombs_points">8</string>

    <string name="risen_nightmare_title">Risen Nightmare</string>
    <string name="risen_nightmare_a">  Gingerly you open the door and step through. You wind your way to a labyrinth of tunnels, half buried forests, underground rivers and dark caves. From deeper caverns you can hear unearthly shrieking.</string>
    <string name="risen_nightmare_b">  If Nazgul of Dol Guldur is not in play, search the encounter deck or discard pile and put him next to the staging area. Shuffle the encounter deck afterwards.\n\tWhen all progress tokens have been placed on this quest, put Nazgul of Dol Guldur into the staging area.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while Nazgul of Dol Guldur is in play. </string>
    <string name="risen_nightmare_points">6</string>

    <string name="goblin_gate_title">Goblin Gate</string>
    <string name="goblin_gate_a">  From here you must break through the dreaded Goblin Gate to get through the woods. An alarm cry goes up and from the gate emerges a swathe of shrieking orcish troops. They have been waiting for you.\n\tEach player searches the encounter deck and places the first orc they find in the staging area. Shuffle the encounter deck afterwards.</string>
    <string name="goblin_gate_b">  The swarm of evil orcs seems unending. You quickly realise you must escape through the gate with post haste. Working your way slowly towards the entrance, you see with a sinking heart that a small army stands fast in your way.\n\tEach player immediately chooses and engages 1 Orc.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while there are Orc cards in play.</string>
    <string name="goblin_gate_points">12</string>

    <string name="elf_path_title">Elf Path</string>
    <string name="elf_path_a">  You march into the darkness of the woods. From the boughs above you a voice calls out. A nimble Elven figure drops to the leafy ground before you. "Hurry - follow me." Your guide darts down a hidden path through the trees and you struggle to keep up.</string>
    <string name="elf_path_b">  You decide to follow the elf through the woods. Behind you evil creatures gather in number and regroup, following hot on your heels. Time is of the essence!\n\tDo not make engagement whilst on this stage. Enemies already engaged with you remain engaged.\n\tYou are neither allowed to engage nor to be engaged by enemies unless you are already engaged with them.</string>
    <string name="elf_path_points">5</string>

    <string name="the_veil_of_the_lonely_mountain_title">The Veil of the Mountain</string>
    <string name="the_veil_of_the_lonely_mountain_a">  In the distance you can see a mountain. Your pursuers emerge around you as you hasten your way to the mountain.\n\tEach player searches the encounter deck and places the first Orc they find into the staging area. Shuffle the encounter deck.</string>
    <string name="the_veil_of_the_lonely_mountain_b">  The Elves have sent help to you. Upon arriving they immediately join you into battle.\n\tEach player may immediately place 1 Elf from their hand into play for free and any Elf character may heal 1 wound. Each player immediately chooses and engages 1 Orc.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while any Orc cards are in play.</string>
    <string name="the_veil_of_the_lonely_mountain_points">10</string>

    <string name="foul_tower_title">Foul Tower</string>
    <string name="foul_tower_a">Your party stumbles upon a dark tower hidden in the thickest undergrowth. With great care you approach the entrance.\n\tSetup: Take out Ungoliant\'s Spawn from the encounter deck and set it to the side out of play. Shuffle the encounter deck afterwards.</string>
    <string name="foul_tower_b">As you work your way through the bushes towards the entrance, Spiders hiss and spit at you from all sides. The thunder of their giant leader coming closer can be heard as you quicken your pace.\n\tWhen 5 progress tokens have been placed on this card, put Ungoliant\'s Spawn into play.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while Ungoliant\'s Spawn is in play.</string>
    <string name="foul_tower_points">10</string>

    <string name="twisted_caverns_title">Twisted Caverns</string>
    <string name="twisted_caverns_a">  You rush into the darkened caverns. Moving carefully through the webbed tunnels. Your route to the surface is cut off.\n\tIf Ungoliant\'s Spawn is not in play, search the encounter deck or discard pile for Ungoliant\'s Spawn and place it to one side out of play.\n\tAllies may no longer enter play or be put into play for the remainder of the whole game.</string>
    <string name="twisted_caverns_b">  From the darkness of the twisting passageways ahead, an enormous shape scuttles to and fro.\n\tWhen 5 progress tokens have been placed on this card, put Ungoliant\'s Spawn into play.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage while Ungoliant\'s Spawn is in play.</string>
    <string name="twisted_caverns_points">10</string>

    <string name="final_stand_title">Final Stand</string>
    <string name="final_stand_a">  The caverns open up into a giant underground spider lair.\n\tIf Ungoliant\'s Spawn is not in play, search the encounter deck or discard pile for Ungoliant\'s Spawn and place it to one side out of play.\n\tAllies and Attachment may no longer enter play or be put into play for the remainder of the game.</string>
    <string name="final_stand_b">  A massive silver thread descends from the ceiling and the spiders around you begin to frenzy as a huge dark shadows fall over you.\n\tWhen 5 progress tokens have been placed on this card, put Ungoliant\'s Spawn into play.\n Players cannot defeat this stage while Ungoliant\'s Spawn is in play.</string>
    <string name="final_stand_points">10</string>

    <string name="the_wounded_eagle_title">The Wounded Eagle</string>
    <string name="the_wounded_eagle_a"> After a fierce conflict with a group of Trolls, you come across a fallen Eagle, grievously wounded and on the verge of death\.\.\.\n\tSetup: Search the encounter deck for Rhosgobel and Wilyador, and add them to the staging area. Then, shuffle the encounter deck.</string>
    <string name="the_wounded_eagle_b">The Eagle\'s wounds cannot be tended in the wilderness, so you attempt to bring the creature to a safe place.</string>
    <string name="the_wounded_eagle_points">8</string>

    <string name="radagasts_request_title">A Dire Request</string>
    <string name="radagasts_request_a">You are asked to head out into the wilderness to find the healing plant, Athelas for the wounded Eagle Wilyador. Meantime, any healing lore or supplies your party has at its disposal could be used to assist in comforting the Eagle until you return.\n\tSetup: If Wilyador is not play, search the encounter deck for Wilyador and place it under control of the first player. Shuffle the encounter deck afterwards. </string>
    <string name="radagasts_request_b">Response: After the quest phase begins, the first player may place X damage tokens on Wilyador to look at the top 3 cards of the encounter deck. Reveal and add 1 of these cards to the staging area, and discard the other 2. X is the number of players in the game.\n\tAction: Once per round, the players may remove claimed Athelas from the game. For each removed Athelas, heal 5 wounds from Wilyador.\n\tPlayers cannot advance this quest phase while Wilyador is wounded.</string>
    <string name="radagasts_request_points">12</string>

    <string name="in_the_forest_title">In the Forest</string>
    <string name="in_the_forest_a">You just defeated some Orcs when you notice more of them incoming. The Orcs have called allies for help as well, and cut off your way back home. You may hide in the forests and recover your strength but you need to find a path to pass the Orcs unnoticed.</string>
    <string name="in_the_forest_b">Forced: Every time 10 cards are drawn from the encounter deck, every player increases his threat by 10.\n\tThis stage can only be defeated if there is no active location.</string>
    <string name="in_the_forest_points">8</string>

    <string name="enchanted_vines_title">Enchanted Vines</string>
    <string name="enchanted_vines_a">Your party finds many hanging vines bearing delicious golden fruit which give off a heady and intoxicating scent. However, the leaves of the vine are covered with a powerful toxin which causes anyone touching them to fall into a deep enchanted sleep. Will any of your group fall victim to the vines?\n\tDraw and discard 1 card from the encounter deck for each ally in play. If the card has a shadow effect listed, return the ally to its controller\'s hand.</string>
    <string name="enchanted_vines_b">If there is currently no Hill Troll in the staging area, search the encounter deck and then the discard pile for a Hill Troll and add it to the staging area. Shuffle the encounter deck.\n\tWhenever you reveal a location from the encounter deck, discard it. Then, each player chooses 1 ally he controls and return it to his hand.\n\tYou may not complete this stage while there is a Hill Troll in play.</string>
    <string name="enchanted_vines_points">2</string>

    <string name="the_secret_tunnel_title">The Secret Tunnel</string>
    <string name="the_secret_tunnel_a">You have reached some old ruins. You find a secret entrance leading to the tunnels below - and hopefully this is not known to the orcs.\n\tIf not yet in play, Search the encounter deck or discard pile for Gandalf\'s map and 2 Cavern Guardians. Place them in the staging area without resolving the guarded keyword. Then shuffle all the treachery and Orc cards currently in the discard pile back into the encounter deck.</string>
    <string name="the_secret_tunnel_b">You force open a secret door, clearly undisturbed for years, and enter the disused tunnel below. Suddenly your path is blocked by two undead guards!\n\tThe players, as a group, may not play more than 1 ally card each round.\n\tIf Gandalf\'s Map is not attached to a questing hero, each questing character has his willpower reduced by 1 during quest resolution.</string>
    <string name="the_secret_tunnel_points">10</string>

    <string name="an_ancient_evil_title">An Ancient Evil</string>
    <string name="an_ancient_evil_a">You are searching through the tunnels, while suddenly your scout comes hurrying back with grim news - a dreadful evil approaches, an undead spirit from a long-past age. It is accompanied by a bodyguard of armoured orc warriors\.\.\.are you strong enough to defeat them?\n\tIf not yet in play, search the encounter deck or discard pile for 2 Dungeon Jailors and Nazgul of Dol Guldur and place them in the staging area.</string>
    <string name="an_ancient_evil_b">The players, as a group, may not play more than 1 ally card each round.\n\tWhile Nazgul of Dol Guldur is in play, all treachery cards gain surge and players may not place progress tokens on this quest stage by any means. You may still place progress tokens on locations as normal.</string>
    <string name="an_ancient_evil_points">12</string>

    <string name="the_hills_of_emyn_muil_title">The Forgotten Hills</string>
    <string name="the_hills_of_emyn_muil_a">Your hunt for the enemy has led you to great waterfalls into jagged unforgiving hills.\n\tSetup: Search the encounter deck for Amon Hen and Amon Lhaw, and add them to the staging area. Then shuffle the encounter deck.</string>
    <string name="the_hills_of_emyn_muil_b">You are certain that the enemy has fled into this area, and you are resolved to explore until you find the fresh trail.\n\tForced: If there are no location cards in the staging area, the first treachery card revealed during the quest phase gains surge.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage unless there are no Emyn Muil locations in play, and they have collected at least 10 victory points</string>
    <string name="the_hills_of_emyn_muil_points">1</string>

    <string name="the_hills_of_emyn_muil_2_title">The Forsaken Hills</string>
    <string name="the_hills_of_emyn_muil_2_a">Your travels have led you into these twisting unnavigable rocky hills.\n\tSetup: Reveal the first X location cards drawn from the encounter deck and add them to the staging area. Discard other cards drawn. X is the amount of players.</string>
    <string name="the_hills_of_emyn_muil_2_b">You are uncertain which way to go, but you are pressing on, intent on finding a way out of this unforgivable maze.\n\tForced: If there are no location cards in the staging area, the first treachery card revealed during the quest phase gains surge.\n\tPlayers cannot defeat this stage unless there are no Emyn Muil locations in play, and they have collected at least 20 victory points</string>
    <string name="the_hills_of_emyn_muil_2_points">1</string>

    <string name="search_for_the_chamber_title">Search in the Depths</string>
    <string name="search_for_the_chamber_a">You are investigating the deep dungeons, searching for a sign of your lost relative. In the heavy twilight of a hall, a bulky tome is discovered in the grip of a skeleton. You carefully take possession of the book. Perhaps it will give you some answers.\..\n\tSetup: Search the encounter deck for Book of Mazarbul and have the first player attach it to a hero of his choice. Shuffle the encounter deck.</string>
    <string name="search_for_the_chamber_b">The runes of the book appear to hold a detailed record of the fledgling colony. But there is some Elvish script at the end which seems out of place. You begin to decipher the runes but are interrupted by a sound from the deep.\..\n\tWhen Revealed: Reveal 1 encounter card per player and add it to the staging area.\n\tWhen this stage is defeated: The final portion of the book tells a grim tale. Your family is slain when they were trapped in the mines. It seems as if there no survivors but you decide to press on. \n\tRemove Book of Mazarbul from the game.</string>
    <string name="search_for_the_chamber_points">15</string>

    <string name="entering_the_mines_title">Entering the Mines</string>
    <string name="entering_the_mines_a">You have been sent to the mines to deliver a message to your allies. Although nobody has seen them for a while./../n/tSetup: Search the encounter deck for East-gate, First Hall and Bridge of Khazad-dûm. Put the East-gate into play as the active location, and put the First Hall and the Bridge of Khazad-dûm aside, out of play. Shuffle the encounter deck.</string>
    <string name="entering_the_mines_b">The doors of the East-gate hang crooked on their hinges. The darkness inside the doorway is still and impenetrable, shutting the last beams of a sinking sun.\n\tWhen Revealed: Reveal 1 encounter card per player, and add it to the staging area.\n\tPlayers cannot advance to the next stage of the scenario unless Bridge of Khazad-dûm is in their victory display.</string>
    <string name="entering_the_mines_points">7</string>

    <string name="a_presence_in_the_dark_title">A Presence in the Dark</string>
    <string name="a_presence_in_the_dark_a">You have discovered the fate of your allies, and seek to leave this dreadful place. But exiting may not be as simple as entering.\..\n\tSetup: Search the encounter deck for The Nameless Fear and all copies of A Foe from Beyond. Add The Nameless Fear to the staging area and shuffle 1 copy of A Foe From Beyond for each player back into the encounter deck.. Shuffle the encounter deck afterwards.</string>
    <string name="a_presence_in_the_dark_b">As you leave, the air grows thick and drums begin to roll from the deeps. A man-shape shadow, yet greater, masses in the distance, and begins to head straight for you.\n\tWhen Revealed: Reveal 1 encounter card per player, and add it to the staging area. Then, add 2 victory points to your victory display count.</string>
    <string name="a_presence_in_the_dark_points">0</string>

    <string name="escape_from_the_darkness_title">Escape from Darkness</string>
    <string name="escape_from_the_darkness_b">There is a weakness in the wall. You can practically taste the freedom beyond.\n\tWhen Revealed: Each player chooses 1 questing character he controls. Each character not chosen does not count its Willpower Strength until the end of the turn. Search the encounter deck and discard pile for Abandoned Tools and add it to the staging area, if able.\n\tAbandoned Tools gains: Refresh Action: Exhaust attached hero to put a progress token on this quest.\n\tProgress tokens cannot be placed on this quest except by Abandoned Tools.</string>
    <string name="escape_from_the_darkness_points">4</string>



<!--General quests-->
    <string name="general_quest_title">The Enemy Draws Near\.\.\.</string>
    <string name="general_quest_a">The presence of the enemy is getting stronger. You press on but you can feel dark powers nearby.</string>
    <string name="general_quest_b">Each player draw a card from the encounter deck and adds it to the staging area.</string>
    <string name="general_quest_points">8</string>

    <!--progress 1-->
    <string name="prisoner_title">Captured!</string>
    <string name="prisoner_a">  While scouting near the enemies former lair, one of your allies was ambushed, captured and is now held in a dungeon cell!</string>
    <string name="prisoner_b">  When Revealed: Randomly select 1 hero card (among all the heroes controlled by the players) and turn it facedown. That hero is now considered a prisoner and cannot be used, damaged or collect resources until it is rescued.\n The players, as a group, cannot play more than 1 ally card each round.\n\tAfter the requirements are met to advance to the next stage, flip the prisoner card face-up and place 1 damage token on it. This hero has been rescued and may now be used by its controller.</string>
    <string name="prisoner_points">10</string>

    <!--progress 2-->
    <string name="unhallowed_title">Uninvited</string>
    <string name="unhallowed_a">You enter the enemy\'s lair. You can now explore the lair but a large party might attract undue attention.</string>
    <string name="unhallowed_b">When Revealed: You may discard any number of allies. Afterwards, reveal 1 encounter card per ally left in play and add them to the staging area.</string>
    <string name="unhallowed_points">4</string>

    <string name="the_fate_of_balin_title">Have Faith!</string>
    <string name="the_fate_of_balin_a">As your party takes a moment to contemplate the impact of your recent experiences, Orc war cries and horns sound close. You cannot tarry and prepare to fight your way out.</string>
    <string name="the_fate_of_balin_b">Forced: At the end of the staging step, reveal the top X cards of the encounter deck, adding all enemies to the staging area. Discard the other revealed cards without resolving them. X is the number of players.</string>
    <string name="the_fate_of_balin_points">17</string>

    <string name="goblin_patrol_title">Goblin Patrol</string>
    <string name="goblin_patrol_a">The skeletons lie undisturbed, but you have discovered no recent signs of allies nearby. The sound of scampering feet travels to your ears, and you move in that direction to investigate. There is a patrol of Goblins, marching in a loose formation through the shadows.</string>
    <string name="goblin_patrol_b1">When Revealed: Each player must search the discard pile for 1 enemy of his choice, and add it to the staging area. One choice must be Patrol Leader, if able.\n\tForced: After an enemy is revealed from the encounter deck, discard it instead of adding it to the staging area.\n\tIf there are no enemies in play, immediately advance to the next stage of the scenario (Players can also advance normally by placing quest tokens on this quest.)</string>
    <string name="goblin_patrol_b2">When Revealed: Each player reveals the first enemy from the encounter deck. Discard other cards drawn.\n\tIf there are no enemies in play, immediately advance to the next stage of the scenario (Players can also advance normally by placing quest tokens on this quest.)</string>
    <string name="goblin_patrol_b3">When Revealed: Each player searches the encounter deck and adds the first goblin enemy to the staging area. Shuffle the encounter deck afterwards. \n\tIf there are no enemies in play, immediately advance to the next stage of the scenario (Players can also advance normally by placing quest tokens on this quest.)</string>
    <string name="goblin_patrol_points">11</string>


    <!--progress 3-->
    <string name="treason_title">Treason</string>
    <string name="treason_a">You found the pass, but it is guarded and closely watched. Obviously the Orcs are looking for you here. Could there be a traitor among you?</string>
    <string name="treason_b">You found the traitor, but he alarmed the enemy! \n\tSetup: Each player places one of his active allies, randomly chosen, in the staging area. He is now an enemy with Engagement Cost 0 and +1 attack. His Willpower Strength is his Threat Strength. Ignore any special abilities on him. \n\tThis stage can only be defeated when no enemies are in the game.</string>
    <string name="treason_points">0</string>

    <string name="ambush_on_the_shore_title">Ambush!</string>
    <string name="ambush_on_the_shore_a">Your enemies have forced you into an ambush! If you survive this, the path to safety should be open.</string>
    <string name="ambush_on_the_shore_b">When Revealed: Reveal 2 encounter cards per player, and add them to the staging area.\n\tSkip the staging step of the quest for the remainder of the game.\n\tOnce there are no enemies in play, the players have won the game.</string>
    <string name="ambush_on_the_shore_points">0</string>

    <string name="a_way_up_title">A Way Up</string>
    <string name="a_way_up_a">You are heading up to the light. The way is treacherous, and you are accompanied by a sense of unease and vague dread.</string>
    <string name="a_way_up_b">Heroes do not collect resources during the resource phase.</string>
    <string name="a_way_up_points">12</string>

    <string name="blocked_by_shadow_title">Search for an Exit</string>
    <string name="blocked_by_shadow_a">As the presence draws near, doubt and fear surround you like a vast shadow. You must find daylight, you must escape.\..\n\tWhile this is the active quest, only click/flip to 2B at the beginning of the staging step.</string>
    <string name="blocked_by_shadow_b">This is a dangerous part of the Mines, but is that light up ahead?\n\tWhen Revealed: Reveal 1 encounter card per player, and add it to the staging area.</string>
    <string name="blocked_by_shadow_points">10</string>


    <string name="progress_1a">1a</string>
    <string name="progress_1b">1b</string>
    <string name="progress_2a">2a</string>
    <string name="progress_2b">2b</string>
    <string name="progress_3a">3a</string>
    <string name="progress_3b">3b</string>
    <string name="information">i</string>
    <string name="select_all">Select All</string>
    <string name="deselect_all">Deselect All</string>

    <string name="scenario_popup_information">These are scenarios similar to the scenario quest cards of the physical game. Before you start to play the generated scenario, you will have to mix the encounter decks with the corresponding symbols as depicted on the screen. Once you have done so, you are ready to play!</string>
    <string name="scenario_popup_title">Scenario Information</string>
    <string name="main_popup_information">This application will generate scenarios to play with The Lord of the Rings Card Game. The application was created with the intent of creating scenarios with a variable combination of encounter sets to have a unique experience every game. To get started, tap all the symbols of the encounter deck you want to play with. You can lock the encounter set by tapping them again. The generator will randomly select 3 to 4 encounter decks from your selection (always including the locked sets) and will create a scenario based on this selection. The generated scenarios are based on already existing scenarios. Note that the quests may not always flow naturally into each other story-wise, so use your creativity to create a coherent story! The difficulty of the generated scenarios should be around level 5 and 6 but this can also vary due to randomness.</string>
    <string name="main_popup_title">Generator Information</string>


    <string name="information_button">information</string>
    <string name="notEnoughToast">Select at least 3 encounter sets</string>
    <string name="tooMuchToast">You cannot lock more than 4 sets</string>

    <string name="spearman_image">spearman</string>
    <string name="goblin_image">goblin</string>
    <string name="book_image">book</string>
    <string name="torch_image">torch</string>
    <string name="fracture_image">fracture</string>
    <string name="pickaxe_image">pickaxe</string>
    <string name="chain_image">chain</string>
    <string name="map_image">map</string>
    <string name="spider_image">spider</string>
    <string name="tree_image">tree</string>
    <string name="orc_image">orc</string>
    <string name="footprint_image">footprint</string>
    <string name="river_image">river</string>
    <string name="eye_image">eye</string>
    <string name="raven_image">raven</string>
    <string name="tower_image">tower</string>
    <string name="hills_image">hills</string>
    <string name="progress_image">image</string>


</resources>
